<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>

  <properties>
    <title>Maven Struts Plug-in</title>
    <author email="dion@multitask.com.au">dIon Gillard</author>
  </properties>

  <body>
    <section name="Maven Struts Plug-in">
      <p>
        This document provides an overview of the Maven Struts Plug-in.
      </p>
      <p>
        The documents presented here are references, if you are looking
        for more verbose usage material, please refer to the <a
        href="../../start/index.html">Getting Started</a> section.
      </p>
      <subsection name="What it is">
        <p>
          The Struts Plug-in is the place where <a 
          href="http://jakarta.apache.org/struts/">Struts</a> tools are found
          in Maven.
        </p>
        <p>
          At the moment it provides a some useful, simple functionality for
          developers who use struts as their web application framework of
          choice. This is in no way a statement by the Maven developers that
          Struts is the best web application framework for your needs, as
          Maven is web app framework agnostic, and will be soon providing
          plug-ins for other frameworks.
        </p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name="Overview of the Struts Plug-in Reference Documentation">
        <table>
          <tr><th>Document</th><th>Description</th></tr>
          <tr><td><a href="build-file.html">Build File</a></td>
            <td>
              This document provides detailed information on the various
              targets that are available as part of the Maven Struts Plug-in.
              These targets can be delegated to by your project's local
              build file.
            </td>
          </tr>
          <tr><td><a href="properties.html">Properties</a></td>
            <td>
              The behavior of the Maven Struts Plug-in can be altered via
              properties.  This document describes each property
              available as the default used.
            </td>
          </tr>
          <tr><td><a href="dirlayout.html">Directory Layout</a></td>
            <td>
              The preferred directory layout structure is documented
              here.  This is a useful document if you are trying to
              determine what a particular component of your directory
              hierarchy is used for.
            </td>
          </tr>
          <tr><td><a href="futures.html">Futures</a></td>
            <td>
              These are the current thoughts on additional items
              that could or should be added to the plug-in.
              They may or may not make it to an actual task list of a
              developer.
            </td>
          </tr>
        </table>
      </subsection>
    </section>
 </body>
</document>
