<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>

  <properties>
    <title>Maven Clover Plug-in</title>
    <author email="vmassol@octo.com">Vincent Massol</author>
  </properties>

  <body>
    <section name="Maven Clover Plug-in">
      <p>
        This document provides an overview of the Maven Clover Plug-in.
      </p>
      <p>
        The documents presented here are references, if you are looking
        for more verbose usage material, please refer to the <a
        href="../../start/index.html">Getting Started</a> section.
      </p>
      <subsection name="What it is">
        <p>
          The Clover Plug-in is the place where <a
          href="http://www.thecortex.net/clover/">Clover</a> tools are found
          in Maven.
        </p>
        <p>
          Clover is a tool that generates Test Coverage reports. It is free for
          non-commercial use. If your project is a commercial project you will
          need to get a license for the Clover jar before using this Plug-in.
        </p>
        <p>
          In order to use this Plug-in you need to place the clover jar in your
          <code>ANT_HOME/lib</code> directory.
        </p>
      </subsection>
      <subsection name="Overview of the Clover Plug-in Reference Documentation">
        <table>
          <tr><th>Document</th><th>Description</th></tr>
          <tr><td><a href="build-file.html">Build File</a></td>
            <td>
              This document provides detailed information on the various
              targets that are available as part of the Maven Clover Plug-in.
              These targets can be delegated to by your project's local
              build file.
            </td>
          </tr>
          <tr><td><a href="properties.html">Properties</a></td>
            <td>
              The behavior of the Maven Clover Plug-in can be altered via
              properties.  This document describes each property
              available as the default used.
            </td>
          </tr>
          <tr><td><a href="dirlayout.html">Directory Layout</a></td>
            <td>
              The preferred directory layout structure is documented
              here.  This is a useful document if you are trying to
              determine what a particular component of your directory
              hierarchy is used for.
            </td>
          </tr>
          <tr><td><a href="futures.html">Futures</a></td>
            <td>
              These are the current thoughts on additional items
              that could or should be added to the plug-in.
              They may or may not make it to an actual task list of a
              developer.
            </td>
          </tr>
        </table>
      </subsection>
    </section>
 </body>
</document>
